Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, but so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
True, our country hasn't seen so much.
as a drop of rain in three years,
but I still put my trust in
the king as I always have.
Most of the country still
has faith in him, actually.
So many times, I tried to
stop them so many times,
but they won't listen to anything I say.
The rebellion isn't stopping.
Their strength,
supplies, and men have reached the limit,
However their intention is to settle
everything once and for all with the next
attack their backs are against the wall
they're stuck in a corner
prepared for death.
Please Vivi you have to stop these fools!
from tearing our country apart.
Where's Laughter?
He's inside.
Toto, old friend, please don't be worried.
Vivi, dear.
We'll succeed.
We're going to stop this.
Thank you, Vivi.
So long, my princess.
We won't see you for a while.
As soon as Yuba's up and
running, stop by, princess.
Yes, of course I will, Toto.
It's gonna be the best town ever.
When it's up and running, I'll
personally give you the grand tour.
See ya, Vivi!
I hope you grow up to become
a great princess someday!
Yay!
Koza, I've notified all of our
contacts in the other towns.
This is it.
The time to strike has finally arrived.
It has.
We aren't nearly as well-armed
as I would like us to be, though.
I know, but there's no other choice now.
We have a duty to protect our country.
No one else can do it.
Only we can.
Don't give up!
We're not beat yet!
Keep fighting!
Stupid kids, Lock here.
Oh, crap. Another one?
Damn it. She's getting away.
Well, Lock there.
She's in the ruins.
Let's get up.
Move it.
What happened?
Hey, boy, what happened to you?
Hey kid, where's Princess Vivi?
Vivi got kidnapped by three men. Oh, no!
Bad guys went in the old ruins.
Koza followed him in there.
He's trying to save the vice leader.
Oh, yeah.
Oh princess, where did you go little
girl, let's play a game, come out,
come out, wherever you are, come out,
come out, I don't see her
anywhere, little Vivi,
you can stop hiding,
we aren't going to hurt you
Found you, little princess.
There you are, girl.
Don't go to run off again on me now.
Gotcha!
Peter!
Vivi, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. Just...
Stay down, punk, unless
you want another beating.
I'll never surrender the
princess. You got that?
Hey, kid, shut your damn mouth
and hand over my meal ticket.
I'm done playing games
with you little brats.
It's a sword. Let's run. Koza!
Don't worry, princess.
He's harmless.
Huh?
Protect her to the death, Sansan Clan!
Leader!
Please stop it!
I'm warning you.
No way, that damn little kid
managed to knock out our boss.
How dare he?
It's time to make that little brat pay.
You.
You're dead, boy.
Take that, bastards.
Papa! You get him.
Princess Vini, are you okay?
You punks!
You desert garbage!
Dare to kid them my daughter!
You dirty swine!
We took care of the other, sire.
Chaka! Pell?
My friends, why are you two here?
That's funny.
We were going to ask
you the same question.
What would drive a king to
travel so far from home?
These areas are a haven for many bandits.
It's not a place for royalty.
Igaram! Kousa's hurt!
Yes, he needs immediate medical attention.
The others are also in
dire need. Pel! Chaka!
Arrange help at once! Sir!
You children acted very brave.
What's wrong, Vivi?
Why are you so distant, child?
I was just so scared.
I was scared, too.
They were so much bigger and stronger
than us and armed to the teeth.
It's not that.
It's just, Leader, you told
them to protect me to the death.
Protect her to the death, Sand Sand Clan!
Don't give your life to save mine. Leader.
Poor Vivi.
Her greatest fear is losing her friends.
Hmm.
Vivi may be a little girl,
but she's also a princess.
Koza, the full measure of gratitude
I owe you cannot be expressed.
So I will simply say, thank you.
But Vivi is one of my friends.
I would do that for all of them.
I see.
Then I'm certain the next generation of
Alabasta's people will be in good hands.
Do you love this country?
Yes.
This is my home.
Mine as well.
Excuse me.
Ma-ma-ma!
There is an important matter
that concerns me greatly.
What's that?
Those who are to lead their
countrymen must be able
to make life and death
decisions without hesitation.
Vivi is far too tender-hearted
for such crushing responsibility.
Sir Igarab. Sire?
Just relax, because as I
see it, Alabasta is safe.
Hmm.
Your Majesty, it is my greatest
desire to serve you until my death.
Yuba?
Exactly, and that news comes directly from
your dad to mine so you know it's true.
Oh wow, that's great!
Your dad asked mine to start a town.
He said it would be
built at the Yuba Oasis.
That's considered the
crossroads of Alabasta.
Where every merchant and
traveler must pass through.
It's the perfect location.
You just wait until it's finished.
This town will bring good fortune
and joy to so many people.
Amazing and that's not even the best part.
My dad is going to be the
mayor of the whole thing.
You're going to Koza of course, but my
dad wants me to stay here in the capital.
He says life will be too hard but I just
gotta be where all the
action is and live it.
I want to help build the
city with my own two hands.
Alabasta will need the
city of Yuba to survive.
We're counting on you, Toto.
Yes, yes. Your majesty.
We'll make Yuba a great city for Alabasta.
So long, my princess.
We won't see you for a while.
As soon as Yuba's up and
running, stop by, princess.
Yes, of course I will.
It's gonna be the best town
ever when it's up and running.
I'll personally give you the grand tour.
Let's move out!
See ya, Vivi.
I hope you grow up to
become a great princess.
Okay.
Koza, stop being so arrogant.
Koza is correct about Yuba.
This new city will bring great
prosperity to the kingdom.
well great job today
everybody really we did
some good work now let's
all lie down on these
comfy beds and get some well-deserved rest
okay we'll need our
strength good night you guys
please this whole trip you've been
nothing but lazy why you quit comparing
me to you and all the other superhuman
freaks now you're annoying me
I think Blue Nose here wins today's award
for laziest talking animal in the desert!
You're sure walking
around in the fur coat!
Sanji, I think that's my bad.
I know, I thought you might have trouble
sleeping here all alone tonight, Veer.
And the award for biggest
perv goes to Sanji.
Alright, slingshot boy.
I'm gonna shove that pillow so far
down your throat you'll choke on it.
You guys don't think to
understand the concept!
I hope you're ready.
Hey, old guy, there's still no water.
My throat's drying up.
How can you stand to live here?
It's horrible.
The water will come.
The Yuba Oasis still has life in it yet.
The dream of Yuba can't be
beaten by a bunch of lousy sand.
The king left this land in my
hands and I will keep it alive.
I'll dig out the sand as
many times as it takes. Oh.
Okay, then, let's dig.
Hey, would you quit your filling the
hole up I spent all this time on? Hm?
I'll never get done with
you filling my holes.
But I'm digging just like you, old guy.
No, I'm digging holes and
you're filling them up.
The sand from the hole you're digging
is going into the hole I'm digging.
In other words, you're not helping.
Ah, a mystery hole, huh?
I said knock it off!
Oh, I give up.
Well, maybe he figured it out now.
The sand stopped coming.
He was able to dig that
in such a short time,
even as tired as he must
be from the journey?
Sleep well tonight, you've earned it.
Food and water.
Pleasant dreams.
Give me a break!
You've got to be kidding me!
How long are we going to have
to wait around like this?
Are you at least going to
offer some refreshments?
I could be practicing my
dance instead of sitting here!
Hoo-hoo-hoo! Mr.
Tu, just sit still over
there and wait quietly.
Yeah!
Shut up, you stupid man!
You calm down, too, Miss Merry Christmas.
I guess it isn't too surprising
that you don't all get along.
Oh, well.
It isn't necessary that you do, anyway.
Miss all Sunday?
Thank you all for coming so far to attend
this gathering of ours in Rain Base.
The city where gambling is the only king,
and every man and woman
dreams of going home rich.
Welcome to Rain Dinners, the
largest casino in the whole city.
Miss All Sunday, could we skip the
formalities and get to the point?
Yes, I was just getting to that, Mr. Wong.
Let's get this started already!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Start, start, start!
Now, now!
Of course, but there's something
that needs to be taken care of.
It's time to meet our boss,
whose face you've never seen.
I've been acting as his face
and his voice for some time now,
delivering orders as he saw fit.
There's no longer any need
for such secrecy, however.
Finally, the time has come.
For Operation Utopia.
It's Crocodile.
This will be the greatest and the final
operation that Baroque Works carries out.
It seems you're familiar with our boss.
Or his public identity, anyway.
Yes, of course we are, but why is
one of the seven warlords leading us?
Yeah, we didn't expect to have
such a big shot guy for our leader!
Let me get this straight, we've been
working for a pirate since the first day!
So then you are actually our boss.
That a problem?
It's not a problem, but
it is a bit confusing.
The Seven Warlords are pirates
sanctioned by the government.
Why would you need a
company like this one?
I do not seek money or status.
It is something more.
Military strength.
Military strength?
Allow me to explain myself.
Let me tell you my true objective,
my goal, and the final operation that
Baroque Works will be conducting.
You mean something like that
really exists on this island?
And we're going to steal the
whole country along with it?
This assignment is making
me tremble all over!
So these new orders are the
final pieces of one giant
plan that Baroque Works
has been working towards?
Yes, that is correct.
Every assignment performed as an agent,
every mission finished
since Baroque Works was
founded has been part
of the single operation.
And those letters there are the
final orders that you will receive.
The time has finally come
for Alabasta Kingdom to
disappear once each of you
has Completed the assignment
you have before you this
desert kingdom will destroy
Itself from the inside
out the rebel and royal
armies will have nowhere
to go Nowhere to turn as
a result they will fall
neatly into the hands of
Baroque Works if all goes
according to plan in a
single night Alabasta Kingdom
will become our utopia.
This mission is the final and
most important act that Baroque
Works will carry out.
Failure is not an option.
We begin tomorrow at
noon. Yes sir! Yes sir!
I wish you luck.
About this Operation Utopia, may I
ask you to postpone it for a while?
How did you get here?
The location of this room is a secret.
So what little hidey-hole did
you crawl out of to get here, Mr.
Three?
Now I will finally complete my mission!
Hold on, Mr. Two.
I didn't crawl out from
anywhere, thank you very much.
I merely followed you all from your
little meeting at Spider's Cafe.
It was easy enough to do.
I just hitched a ride on the
back of Bunchy's car unseen.
Boss, at last we meet.
I have come here to humbly
beg for your forgiveness.
And to ask that I may be
given a second chance!
You see, Mr. True,
I knew that it was only a matter of time
Before someone was sent to eliminate me.
After I failed to complete the
assignment that I was given.
That is why I made the decision
to change my course slightly.
And head directly for our
headquarters at the Spider's Cafe.
You said you had failed
to complete a mission?
What are you talking about?
Well, you know?
How I was unfortunately unable
to prevent the Straw Hat Brats.
and Princess Vivi from escaping, remember?
You're telling me that they got away.
All of them.
You're saying that they're still alive?
What were you talking about
on the transponder snail?
You said that they were dead.
Princess Vivi and her bratty
little pirate friends.
You did deal with them, didn't you?
A transponder snail?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I never used a transponder snail the
entire time I was on Little Garden,
not even once. What?
Yeah, hello?
You've reached the Crab Café.
Can I take your order?
This isn't good news,
although it does explain why the Unluckies
haven't returned from Little Garden.
I assume you at least got
rid of one or two of them.
No, not exactly.
Wait!
The information I was given
wasn't entirely accurate!
There were four pirate
escorts with Princess Phoebe.
And then on top of that, there was this
really funny-looking man with a long...
Damn it!
Oh, please, boss.
Can you explain to the rest of us
what's going on with all this insanity?
None of this makes any sense!
All of them!
I met all of these people!
Yes, I ran into them
on my way to the cafe!
Really?
There was this guy, and
this guy, and this girl,
and this guy, and this thing too,
plus one more.
So Miss Wednesday is really a
princess posing as an agent?
You mean these people are
all actually the enemy?
That's correct.
These people haven't
covered who I really am.
They need to be taken care of, or
they'll interfere with the plan.
Mr.
Three, you're right about one thing.
It does seem like they have
added one person and one animal.
Their group is increasing in number
as they continue to move forward.
Setting the pet aside,
I think there is something that we
can safely assume at the moment.
Princess Vivi and her four little friends
are very likely in Alabasta already.
Now to prepare. Mr.
Two, make photos of those
faces you displayed.
But, but boss,
I promise that I will eliminate Vivi
and her friends with my own two hands!
Just shut up, you damn fool!
Now, Mr.
Three, listen very carefully.
Do you have any idea why
I gave you your ring?
Why you're an officer agent, hmm?
In terms of fighting
skills alone, even Mr.
Four has you beat.
Do you understand that?
I promoted you because of your underhanded
tenacity when it comes to
completing an assignment.
You have greatly disappointed me.
What's happening to him?
He's just shriveling up.
Water!
I need water!
Some water!
You can have all the water you want.
Down there.
It looks to be feeding time.
Where am I now? Underwater.
It looks almost like a giant aquarium.
I'm at the gate door!
Nothing but trouble.
But no longer.
Now the rest of you listen up!
Take a good look at these five.
They are determined to stop
the rebellion in Alabasta.
If we leave them alone, they
are bound to come to us.
I understand that.
But boss, even if the girl is
the princess of this country?
Do you really think that she can
prevent the Rebellion at this point?
Unfortunately, she has a connection
that she can take advantage of.
Princess Vivi Nefertari
and the Rebel leader Koza
were apparently friends
when they were children.
The Rebels have 700,000.
Even if the Rebellion
can't be stopped now,
Princess Vivi is certainly capable of
bringing real confusion to their ranks.
I've already sent many of the billions
to join with Koza's Rebel forces.
The fact that I haven't heard
anything from our men must
mean that Vivi and her friends
have not yet taken any action.
This is good.
Whatever the cost,
they must be prevented
from making contact with
the Rebel Army before the
operation is complete,
and we have won.
Miss Allsunday. Sir.
Given the current circumstances,
we should use transponder snails.
Contact the billions who are in Nanohana.
Tell them to kill on sight
without any hesitation.
Do not allow Princess Vivi
and the pirates into Katorea!
Vivi must not be allowed to
meet with the rebel leader Koza!
Yes, sir.
Now the rest of you get going as well.
You don't want to miss the fun, do you?
We are very close to realizing our utopia.
I'd hate to be disappointed by any of you.
You understand just
leave it to us boss sir
Go enjoy yourselves
I'm so sorry.
I didn't have more to
offer you princess Vivi.
No, please don't worry about it Well, we
should be off now Toto. Oh Luffy. Here.
Take this with you
Whoa! Water! Water!
You found some, then? Yes,
it was last night a bit after you fell
asleep while digging that huge hole of yours.
I finally reached a moist
layer under the dry stuff.
That water there is the moisture that I
was able to extract from the damp sand.
Whoa!
That sounds pretty
complicated, but thank you.
That right there is genuine Yuba water.
It's not much, but it's all
I was able to get. Right.
Then I'll drink it with care.
Huh?
Hey, Luffy, what are you doing over there?
Luffy?
Um, is everything all right?
I quit.
Huh?
What do you mean?
What's that mean?
Quit what, Luffy?
Oh, come on.
We don't have time to put up with every
weird little mood you have right now, Luffy.
Let's go.
Yeah, shouldn't we get going?
Yes, we should and fast.
If we don't get back to
that Katorea place the way
we came and stop the rebellion
that's about to begin,
then a million Alabasta
citizens are gonna start
fighting and things will
get real ugly real quick.
We're doing this for Vivi.
So, let's go.
What is wrong with you?!
Vivi? Yes?
Right now, all I want to do is kick
Crocodile's ass, you understand?
Maybe we can keep the people
from starting a rebellion,
but that won't stop Crocodile.
Besides, we won't be able to
accomplish anything in Katorea.
We're pirates, everyone knows things
are better off without us around.
You gotta admit,
he has a way of getting straight to
the point when he really wants to.
Well yeah but not often no that's not
true you want it to work out so that
nobody dies in this fight isn't that
right Vivi none of the citizens none of
us either we're up against one of the
seven warlords of the sea and a million
of your own people on top of that and
you still want everyone to end up all?
safe and sound.
You'll never win that way.
Come on, Luffy.
Can't you at least try showing
Vivi a little sympathy?
Wait, hold on, Nami. For what?
And what's wrong with that, huh?
What is so wrong about
not wanting to see people
die or get hurt?
Because people die, that's why.
Stop talking like that!
I won't listen to it!
Say that again and I will really hurt you!
That's the whole point of what we're
doing here, don't you understand?
No one here in Alabasta,
not the rebel army,
the royal army, or the
people is to blame for this!
None of them have done anything wrong!
Why should any of them have
to pay for what's happened
when every last bit of
it is Crocodile's fault?
So you're saying it's only
all right for you to die?
No, Luffy, you've gone too far!
Damn it, Luffy!
Just being in this country one day and
taking a look around, even I can tell!
Tell what?
What this country needs
more than anything!
This Oasis has life in it yet.
The dream of Yuba can't be
beaten by a bunch of lousy sand.
Do you think that
putting just your life on
the line is enough to
stop this from happening?
Well, what else exactly should I be
putting on the line with it then, Luffy?
I can't let him get away with this.
What, Luffy?
I don't have anything else I can
put on the line. Just... just me.
Well, you can at least try putting
all of our lives on the line together!
Aren't we friends, huh?
Well, aren't we friends?
There.
Now you see.
Now you understand.
Hey, you can cry.
We'll succeed.
We're going to stop this.
I know how much you hate this.
You want to get crocodile the most.
So now tell me!
Where can I find Crocodile?!